{"data":[{"question":"Most stories will accept a credit card instead by cash.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Most","b":"will accept","c":"instead by","d":"cash","answer":"3","explain":"- Instead by-> instead of","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"Our opinions on the subject is identical.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Our opinions","b":"on","c":"is","d":"identical","answer":"3","explain":"- Is-> are","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"Local residents said they are against the new traffic scheme.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Local","b":"are","c":"against","d":"traffic","answer":"2","explain":"- Are-> were","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"Mandy is exciting about going to Greece on holiday.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"exciting","b":"about","c":"to","d":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- Exciting-> excited","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"I would like to thank your brother of his help.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"would like","b":"to thank","c":"of","d":"help","answer":"3","explain":"- Of-> for","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"Harry's parents were not pleased for his failure in the final examination.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Harry's parents","b":"pleased","c":"for","d":"final","answer":"3","explain":"- For-> with","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"Please forgive me for broke your camera.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"forgive","b":"me","c":"broke","d":"your camera","answer":"3","explain":"- Broken-> broking","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"It would be nice to able to fly a plane.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"would be","b":"nice","c":"to able to","d":"fly a plane","answer":"3","explain":"- To able to-> to be able to","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"Don't shout all the time, it's so be annoying!\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Don't shout","b":"all the time","c":"so","d":"be annoying","answer":"4","explain":"- Be annoying-> annoying","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"},{"question":"I regrets not going to university.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"regrets","b":"not","c":"going","d":"to","answer":"1","explain":"- Regrets-> regret","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"24","type":"1"}]}